Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
- Recordings
  - Lawrence Widdoes: "Sanctus", SATB - Piano, Pro Arte Chamber Singers, 1973; gss_832; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Lejaren Hiller, 1974; gss_105; A portfolio for diverse performers and tapes (1974); 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - Les Noces (1), gss_543; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
  - Les Noces (2), gss_542; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
  - Les Noces Orchestra I (1), gss_815; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Les Noces Orchestra I (2), gss_816; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Les Noces Orchestra I Session (3), gss_817; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Les Noces, Cimbalom, gss_841; Note on the box reads: "rough cut".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Lewis - Austin (test copy), gss_762; Note on the back of the box reads: "Three Players" of Jane Austin"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Liblar (1), gss_324; Recording of different music same instrumentation and vocal style, with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    101-108: cont'd from 325 with different music same instrumentation and vocal style, Libby asked opinions; 109-115: (cello or viola)
  - Liblar (2), gss_325; Recording of clarinet, bass, drums, piano, clapping, stomping, soprano, tenors with discussion at the end.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    201-217: "Do do da do do ..."(clarinet, bass, drums, piano, clapping, stomping, soprano, tenors)
  - Lou Harrison: "Mass", 04/08/1976; gss_835; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Douglas] Moore: "Gallantry" (2), gss_851; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Douglas] Moore: Gallantry, gss_264; "Gallantry" is a one act opera by [Douglas] Moore; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
    (orchestra, soprano, tenor, baritone)
  - [Douglas] Moore: Gallantry (1), gss_254; "Gallantry" opera by composer Douglas Moore; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Slates: 301-303: "And now once again walking by" (orchestra, soloist); 304 "Listen to me Lula" (orchestra, soloist); 305/401-402: "Well..." (orchestra, soloist); 403-410: (orchestra, soloist); 501-506: (orchestra, soloist)
  - Moravian (edited), gss_778; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    Group I: 1 - O There's a sight (00); 2 - I will make an everlasting (70); 3 - My savior lies in angulsh [?] (120); 4 - O, Be glad [?] (230); Group II: 1 - ? (320); 2 - Look how beautiful (400); 3 - God was in Jesus (545); 4 - It is our God (685); 5 - I will freely sacrifice
  - [Edmund] Najera; [Lou] Harrison, gss_934; Two tapes in the same box (gss_933 and gss_934).; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
    Edmund Najera: In Dulci Jubilo
  - Naughty Smith (1), gss_110; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - Naughty Smith (2), gss_111; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - Naughty Smith (3); O. Monteverdi, gss_112; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - Naughty, Smith (1), gss_048; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: Music of Victor Herbert's Operetta "Naughty Marietta" taken of "Italian street song", Ros sings Marietta".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (10), gss_057; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Naughty Marietta". Takes and pickups of "I'm Falling in Love with Someone" (duet with orchestra); Takes of "If I were Anybody Else But Me" (duet with orchestra)."; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (11), gss_058; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Naughty Marietta". Takes and pickups of "If I Were Anybody Else But Me"; Take of "Ah, Sweet Mystery of Life" (Dream Melody) (duet with orchestra and chorus) and "Italian Street Song" (Sounds like finale)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (12), gss_059; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Naughty Marietta". Take of "Ah, Sweet Mystery of Life" (Dream Melody) (duet with orchestra and chorus) and "Italian Street Song" (finale?); Pickups: takes of "It's Pretty Soft for Simon".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (13), gss_060; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Naughty Marietta". Take of "It's Pretty Soft for Simon"; Pickups and takes of Intermezzo "Italian Street Song", "Ah, Sweet Mystery of Life"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (14), gss_061; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Naughty Marietta". Pickups of Ah, Sweet Mystery of Life", Intermezzo; Takes of "Live For Today" (waltz song, trio with orchestra)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (15), gss_062; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Naughty Marietta". Pickups and takes of "Live For Today" (waltz song, trio with orchestra)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (16), gss_063; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Naughty Marietta". Pickups or take of "Live For Today" (trio with orchestra); Overture orchestra pickup; pickups, violin solo "Ah, Sweet Mystery of Life".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (2), gss_049; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: Music of Victor Herbert's Operetta "Naughty Marietta". 1 Take of "Italian street song"; Takes of "In Never Never can be Love".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (3), gss_050; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: Music of Victor Herbert's Operetta "Naughty Marietta". Takes of "In Never Never can be Love"; Takes of "Neath the Southern Moon".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (4), gss_051; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: Music of Victor Herbert's Operetta "Naughty Marietta". Takes of "Neath the Southern Moon"; Takes of "Tramp, Tramp, Tramp".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (5), gss_052; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: Music of Victor Herbert's Operetta "Naughty Marietta". Takes of "Neath the Southern Moon"; Takes "Naughty Marietta" retakes."; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (6), gss_053; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: Music of Victor Herbert's Operetta "Naughty Marietta". Takes of "Naughty Marietta" and pickups."; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (7), gss_054; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: Music of Victor Herbert's Operetta "Naughty Marietta". Takes and pickups of Overture "Tramp, Tramp, Tramp" - "I'm Falling in Love with Someone"; "All Sweet Mystery of life" (Dream Melody); "Italian Street Song"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (8), gss_055; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: Music from Victor Herbert's Operetta "Naughty Marietta". "All Sweet Mystery of life" (Dream Melody); "Italian Street Song" (orchestra excused here). Dread Melody for solo violin (piece cups); "I'm Falling In Love with Someone", Tenor with orchestra soprano (Roz)."; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - Naughty, Smith (9), gss_056; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Naughty Marietta". Takes of "I'm Falling in Love with Someone"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 5)
  - New Year's Eve (1), gss_796; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    "Bay Psalm No. 39" ([Rosalind] Rees, [Priscilla]Magdamo, [Thomas] Bogdan, [Richard] Muenz; Despair" ([Rosalind] Rees, [Priscilla]Magdamo, [Thomas] Bogdan, [Richard] Muenz; [Francis] Hopkinson: "My love has come" [Rosalind] Rees, Richmand
  - New Year's Eve (2), gss_797; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    [Francis] Hopkinson: "Beneath a weeping willow"; "See down Maria's cheek"
  - New Year's Eve (3), gss_798; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    [Francis] Hopkinson: "My gen'rous heart"; "The traveler"; "Come Fair Rosina"; "Enraptured"
  - New Year's Eve (4), gss_799; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    [Francis] Hopkinson: "My Days Have Been So Wondrous Free"
  - Nominee: Rees, Rosalind (699-0610), gss_769; This is a dub for Riverside Ratio WRVR Program: Vocal Recital - Rosalind Rees, Katherine Hoover, flute. Series: Russel: 2 Songs (For flutist). Inserted in the box is a letter from Rosalind Rees with list of the recordings to the Ford Foundation, Program for Concert Artists. Jan 29 [no year]; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
    1: "Das Marienleben", Paul Hindemith (4 reels) - life performance; 2: "Deux poèmes du Ronsard", Roussel (tape record for radio broadcast WVRV, New York City); 3: "Five Canons, Op. 16, Anton Webern, Webern is first taping for an all Webern vocal album for Everest Record
  - Nominee: Rees, Rosalind (699-0610) (1st), gss_746; On the back of the box there is a label from WHA Recording Service.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Nominee: Rees, Rosalind (699-0610) (2nd), gss_747; On the back of the box there is a label from WHA Recording Service.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Nominee: Rees, Rosalind (699-0610) (3rd), gss_748; On the back of the box there is a label from WHA Recording Service.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Nominee: Rees, Rosalind (699-0610) (4th), gss_749; On the back of the box there is a label from WHA Recording Service.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Nominee: Rees, Rosalind (699-0610) (unmarked), gss_750; Note on the box reads: "Webern; 7 1/2 ips, 2 tracks stereo, one way only."; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - NYK - St. Peter's; [Johann Sebastian] Bach No. 32, Rochberg; NYK (beginning of concert): [Gustav] Holst; Wims; Rochberg, [Richard] Wagner, 01/07/1973; gss_919; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Oversize 61)
  - NYK Performance - St. Peter's; Xmas [Christmas] cantata, [Anton] Webern rehearsal; [Johan Sebastian] Bach: Cantata, 06/01/1971; gss_920; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Oversize 61)
  - O. Monteverdi (4), gss_113; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - O'Hairs (1), gss_238; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates: 101-105: Children chorus, mixed chorus with piano and soprano, xylophone, percussion, sfx, other, spoken male dialogue - G. S. says "We lots Joe", recording aborted
  - O'Hairs (2), gss_239; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    "Lucas" (Foss?) mentioned; (Cont'd from 238) Slates: 201-205: "Elephants Balls, C[?] Clock..."; 206-207: "A cat swung by its tail"
  - O'Hairs (3), gss_240; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates: 301-302: "In the beat..." (soprano, other sounds, some pre-recorded, roll-ins); 303-306: "How firmly..." (soprano, other sounds); 306-309: "Drop dead..." (soprano, other sounds); 310-312: "There is no..." (soprano, other sounds)
  - O'Hairs (4), gss_241; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates: 401-406: "There is a sunset..." (cont'd from 240
  - Omaggio (1), gss_695; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - Omaggio (2), gss_696; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - Omaggio (3), gss_697; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - Omaggio (4), gss_698; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - Omaggio (5), gss_699; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - Outtakes from Scandanavia Recording, 06/08/1983; gss_884; Note on the box reads: "Including truck horn at end of Rautavaara".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    1 - "O Bone Jesu", Bernhard Lewkovitch, pianist; 2 - "Malaguena" from [Frederico Garcia] Lorca suite, Einojuhani Rautavaara (Finish composer); 3 - "Upphoff", Thorkell Sigurbjörnsson (Icelandic composer)
  - Piston, Walter: "Psalm and Prayer of David" (1), gss_813; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Piston, Walter: "Psalm and Prayer of David" (2), gss_814; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Prelim Editing; New Xmas [Christmas] Album, gss_755; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Psalm 150; Diffusa est gratia; De profudis, gss_623; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
    1: Psalm 150 (1:35); 2: Diffusa est gratia (Madrigal choir) (2:25); 3: Mattheus en de rijkdom; 4: De Profudis (Belgian Radio and Television choir de Vic Nees, Andre Laporte) (7:40); Mattheus en de rijkdom (Radio choir de Vic Nees) (11:00)
  - Randall Thompson: "Alleluia", 04/08/1976; gss_842; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Red Mill (1), gss_693; Note on the box reads: "(1) Red Smith, 7 1/2 IPS and 805. Go while the going is good". May be this is a recording of "The Red Mill" operetta by Victor Herbert.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Red Mill (2), gss_694; Note on the box reads: "(1) Red Smith, 7 1/2 ips". May be this is a recording of "The Red Mill" operetta by Victor Herbert.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Reel 1: I: Deuche - Freuet euch (O Be Glad); II. Johan Peter: Ever lasted covenant; III. [Georg] Muller - My Savior (con't on Reel 2), gss_638; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - Reel 2: III: Simon Peter: "O Anblick" (O, There's a sight); IV: Georg Muller: "Mein Heiland" (My Savior), gss_639; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - Reel 3: V: It is finished, gss_640; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 50)
  - Reifanac, gss_615; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Renwick (3), gss_935; Note on the box reads: "NB last piece (Mockingbird) first women duet should be replaced by copy of second".; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
  - Renwick (3), gss_936; Note on the box reads: "NB last piece (Mockingbird) first women duet should be replaced by copy of second".; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)
  - Renwick 1 and 2 (1), gss_800; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 3 and 4 (2), gss_801; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 5 and 6 (3), gss_802; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 7 and 8 (4), gss_803; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 15 and 17 (8), gss_804; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 17 and 20 (9), gss_805; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 20 and 23 (10), gss_806; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 23 and 26 (11), gss_807; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 26 and 29 (12), gss_808; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 29 and 32 (13), gss_809; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 32 and 35 (14), gss_810; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 35 and 37 (15), gss_811; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Renwick 38 and 39 (16), gss_812; Recorded in the Renwick Art Gallery in Washington DC.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Requiem for a City, Sound effects Tape, gss_880; Note on the box reads: "This is a DUB of the edited master - this is the same tape use for the Gregg Smith recording. This tape is to be used as the Dubbing master".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - [Roger] Reynolds: "Blind Men", gss_776; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Richards (12), gss_250; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Slates: 1201-1206: ? (soloists, chorus); 1207-1208: "From the beginning" (soloists, chorus)
  - Richards (13), gss_251; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Slates (All the same music): 1301-1315: ? (soloists); 1316-1318: "Son/sun" (?) (mixed chorus)
  - Richards (14), gss_252; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Slates: 1401-1417
  - Richards (15), gss_253; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Slates (same music): 1501-1507: ? (women's choir, men's choir); 1508-1512: "Strong clouds" (women's choir, men's choir)
  - Richards "Thought", gss_262; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
  - [Dennis] Riley Summer Music, gss_186; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Flute, guitar, soprano".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 15)
  - [Dennis] Riley Winter Music (master), gss_185; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "All instrumental music, 2 violins or 3)".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 15)
  - [Dennis] Riley; Roz (master), gss_187; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 15)
    1: I'm Nobody" (Roz, piano); 2: "About"; 3: "You Seed Within...."; 4-7 (might all be one piece)
  - Rorem - Roxbury, gss_538; Recording of tenor, chorus, soprano, bass without accompaniment.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    2: Gloria in Excelsis Deo; 3: Sanctus; 4: Husanna in Excelsis Deo; 5: Dona Nobis Pacem; 6: There is no alleluia
  - Rorem - Stevens Last poems, gss_859; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this could be a recording of Last Poems of Wallace Stevens.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - [Ned] Rorem (3), 11/03/1975; gss_917; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
    Sanctus
  - [Ned] Rorem: Roz; Jerry (1), gss_854; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Ned] Rorem; [Rosalind] Reels (1) CD, gss_438; Recording of soprano with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    1-11: Hallelujah ... hallelujah... hallelujah
  - [Ned] Rorem; [Rosalind] Reels (2) CD, gss_439; Performance of soprano with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    1-2/4-6/8/11/13-15: ?; 3: "Such beauty..."; 7: "Driver what street is this..."; 9: "The other night I saw a light"; 10: "Sometimes with one I love"; 12: "I am rose"
  - [Ned] Rorem; [Rosalind] Reels (3) CD, gss_440; Performance of soprano, tenor, baritone, alto with piano accompaniment and orchestra.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    1: ‘Early in the morning; 2: "What a physical effect it has on me..." (conversation duet with orchestra); 4: "Down at the docks..."; 5: "Let's take a walk in the city..."
  - Roroz (1), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_353; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Slates: 101-104: "Among them..." (piano and Roz -soprano solo)
  - RoRoz (1), 05/14/1982; gss_861; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Roroz (10), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_362; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    1001-1009: (viola or cello, piano duet); 1010: (viola or cello, piano duet with soprano)
  - Roroz (11), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_363; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    1101-1109: (viola or cello, piano, soprano solo)
  - Roroz (12 and 13), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_364; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    1201-1204: "It was ..." (piano, cello or viola, soprano); 1206-1208: "There is ..." (piano, cello or viola, soprano); 1209-1214: ? (piano, cello or viola, soprano); 1215/1301-1305: "It is ..." (piano, cello or viola, soprano)
  - Roroz (2), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_354; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Contd. from 353: Slates: Piano and Roz; 201: airplane; 202-207: "Among the old men..."
  - RoRoz (2), 05/14/1982; gss_862; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Roroz (3), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_355; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Contd. from 354: Slates: Piano and Roz; 301: "Among the old men"; 302-307: "... was glad he had written his poems" (viola, bass, piano)
  - Roroz (4), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_356; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    Slates: 401-408: Cont'd from 355 "Poem"
  - RoRoz (4), 05/14/1982; gss_863; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Roroz (5), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_357; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    Slates: 501-503: Cont'd from 356 "Poems"; 504-506: (viola or cello, piano, instrumental duet)
  - Roroz (6), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_358; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    Cont'd from 357: 601-603: (viola or cello, piano duet); 604-608: (soprano solo)
  - Roroz (7), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_359; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    Cont'd from 358: 701-702: (viola, or cello, piano, soprano); 703-709: (soprano acapella)
  - Roroz (8), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_360; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    Cont'd from 359: 801-802 (soprano accapella); 803-807: "Shined" (soprano accapella); 808-809: (soprano solo, piano, viola or cello)
  - Roroz (9), 04/02/1983; 04/03/1983; 04/04/1983; 04/05/1983; gss_361; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
    901-905: (soprano solo, viola or cello, piano)
  - Rosalind Rees Vocal Recital with Katherine Hoover, flute, Stanley Hoffman, violin and String Ensemble, 03/27/1970; gss_770; This is a dub for Riverside Ratio WRVR Program: Rosalind Rees Vocal Recital with Katherine Hoover, flute, Stanley Hoffman, violin and String Ensemble.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    1: Vaughan Willimas: 8 Hesnman songs (16:56); 2: Russel: 2 Rensard Songs (6:30); 3: Weigl: Sextet - voice and strings (9:20)
  - [Ronald] Roxbury: Leda, gss_260; Opera "Leda and the velvet gentleman" by Ronald Roxbury; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
  - [Ronald] Roxbury; [William] Schuman, gss_878; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - [Ronald] Roxbury, Baltimore, Smith, TBC Sanctus, gss_261; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
  - Roz - GSS; Coplinson, gss_549; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 44)
  - Roz - Webern, gss_753; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Roz [Rosalind Rees] Gift (1), gss_426; Recording of oboes, finger cymbal, soprano, harp, tambourine, drum performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    101-103: (oboes, finger cymbal, soprano, harp, tambourine, drum); 104-105: (oboes); 106-117: (oboes, finger cymbal, soprano, harp, tambourine, drum)
  - Roz [Rosalind Rees] Gift (2), gss_427; Recording of bassoon oboe, finger cymbal, soprano harp, tambourine, drum performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    Cont'd from 426: 201-222: (bassoon oboe, finger cymbal, soprano harp, tambourine, drum)
  - Roz [Rosalind Rees] Gift (3), gss_428; Recording of bassoon oboe, finger cymbal, soprano, harp, tambourine, drum performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    Cont'd from 427: 301-320: (bassoon oboe, finger cymbal, soprano, harp, tambourine, drum)
  - Roz [Rosalind Rees] Gift (4), gss_429; Recording of bass oboe, finger cymbal, soprano, harp, tambourine, drum performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    Cont'd from 428: 401-418: (bassoon oboe, finger cymbal, soprano, harp, tambourine, drum)
  - Roz [Rosalind] Rees, [ Randall] Thompson, gss_002; Soprano with harp and clarinet accompanying.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 1)
  - Roz/ Ralph, gss_267; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
    (Piano, soprano Roz): " ... you left an hour ago..." "In a dream I had last night"
  - Rozard (1), gss_484; Recording of soprano solo with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 38)
    101-103: (piano, soprano solo)
  - Rozard (2), gss_485; Recording of soprano solo with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    Contd. from 484: 201-210: "It's like you left an hour ago..." (piano, soprano)
  - Rozard (3), gss_486; Recording of soprano solo with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    Contd. from 485: 301-307: "It's like you left an hour ago..." (piano, soprano); 308-309: "Last night's dream" (piano, soprano)
  - Rozard (4), gss_487; Recording of soprano solo with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    Contd. from 486: 401-411: "Last night's dream" (piano, soprano)
  - Rozrem (1), 03/18/1983; gss_848; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is could be a recording of Rosalind Rees Sings Ned Rorem – with the composer at the piano.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - RozRem (1), 03/25/1983; gss_855; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is could be a recording of Rosalind Rees Sings Ned Rorem – with the composer at the piano.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)